

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address

os. Kolorowe 4/12 31-938 Kraków

Contact

+48 696 051 742

teresa.j.gajewska@gmail.com

SOFTWARE SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS



Bootstrap 4



JavaScript, jQuery



Angular, TypeScript



GIT



Adobe Photoshop



LANGUAGES

English (CAE Cert.)





HOBBIES



Bicycle touring (Europe, Asia)



Backpacking

TERESA GAJEWSKA

PROFILE

Over the last four years I have worked in the web development company, where I cooperated with developers and I became familiar with their job. Some time ago, I decided to change my career path. I began by learning the fundamentals of front-end technologies, such as HTML, CSS, SCSS, and JavaScript. Over the last few months I have been creating the front-end layer of a variety of web pages for my current employer.

I am actively in search of new career opportunities as a web developer.

PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS:

- szwajcariakaszubska.com
- "Żnin County" (unpublished yet)
- "Czas na Świętokrzyskie" (unpublished yet)
- "Obserwator żubrów" (unpublished yet)

SIDE PROJECTS:

https://github.com/tgajewska

EXPERIENCE

06.2018 - present

Amistad Sp. z o.o.

front-end developer creating front-end layer of web pages (HTML, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery)

2014 - 2018

Amistad Sp. z o.o.

project manager

coordination of the work of the publishing and software development departments

2013 - 2014

Panczakiewicz Art Design

graphic designer, desktop publishing worker

2008 - 2013

First work experiences

project manager in Bezdroża Publishing House (2008-2010), payment processing at HSBC Service Delivery (2012-2013)

EDUCATION

2003 - 2008

Jagiellonian University, Kraków

Polish philology, master degree